pens.com 2006-06-20

# Privacy

|   
---  
  
**Privacy Policy**

> National Pen Company, the sponsor of Pens.com, has created this Privacy Statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This statement outlines our information gathering and sharing practices for this web site. 

**

Information We Collect and How We Use It

**

> When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. This information enables us to process and fulfill your order, and to notify you of your order status. 

> Information about the activity of visitors to this site is tracked automatically when you sign in. We use this information for internal review in aggregate. We maintain strict security over all the information you share with us and use this information in support of your customer relationship with us and to improve your shopping experience: 

> 1) In the future, we may personalize your shopping experience by using your information on purchases to guide our recommendations of items that might interest you. Only Pens.com, or people working on behalf of Pens.com, will send you these communications. 

> 2) We monitor customer traffic patterns and web site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the online store. 

> 3) Occasionally, we may use the information we collect to notify you of important functionality changes to the web site, Pens.com services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. 

> 4) In the future, we may make some limited name and address information available to other organizations that provide goods or services that we feel may be of interest to you. 

> You can opt out of receiving further marketing promotions at any time. Just e-mail us at [Sales@pens.com ](mailto:Sales@pens.com)or notify us when you give us your personal information. 

> **Other Important Information About Privacy**

> You can maintain an online account consisting of your e-mail address and a personal password, to order items and use services we offer on our web site. Please be careful whenever you're online. Your password is yours and should not be shared with anyone else. If, at any time, you want to change the e-mail address and password or other profile information please email [webmaster@pens.com](mailto:webmaster@pens.com) with the specific information you would like to change. 

**

Use of "Cookies"

**

> "Cookies" are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually prevent accepting cookies by changing your browser settings. 

> A cookie allows you to browse in the store, put items in your shopping cart and then return several days later to continue where you left off - with the previously selected items still in the cart. Cookies help us give you a better web site, by letting us monitor what's working and what isn't through site traffic analysis. Please be assured that accepting a cookie does not give us access to your computer or personal information under any circumstances.

**Your Consent**

> By using our web site, you agree that Pens.com may collect and use this information in the manner described above. We will post the changes to our privacy policy on this page so that you are always informed about what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**How We Protect Customer Information**

> When you place an order, access your account information, or send us personally identifying data, that information moves into a secure server. The "Secure Server Software" (SSL) encrypts all information you input before sending it, protecting your information from unauthorized access. ****

**

Security Policy

**

> We know you want secure online ordering. That's why Pens.com uses "Secure Socket Layers" ("SSL"), an industry standard encryption technology that protects your credit card information. SSL encrypts all ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so it cannot be read in transit. The secure area of our web site displays a prefix of https:// and the browser should show a lock or key symbol. As required by law under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your credit card issuer must limit your liability to $50 in the extremely rare case of confirmed credit card fraud. When you place an order with Pens.com, a Federally Insured and Accredited Banking Institution manages the credit card processing.
